ADEBANJO OLALEKAN BABAJIDE

A dedicated Software Engineer with one year experience looking forward to acquiring more tech skills, growing and making a great impact in the tech space. Also passionate about impacting knowledge, growth in the society having great listening and administrative skills.

Contact: +2348088643372

Address: Lagos, Nigeria.

Mail: oadebanjo99@gmail.com
github:https://github.com/olalekan9

9

EXPERIENCE

SAIL Tech Program: Trainee

February 2023 – July 2023

Application using Html, CSS, JavaScript and Node JS

Zuri Cohort Bootcamp 2022 - Trainee

October 2022 - November 2022

Basic knowledge in frontend development using Html, CSS.

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Maltida Michael Fashion House, Lekki, Lagos — Pattern Maker

August 2022 - December 2022

Production of patterns for garment production.

Martwayne School of Fashion, Surulere, Lagos — Trainer

January 2018- March-2022

Served as the head trainer, tasked with the administrative skills in the company.

National Youth Service Corp; NYSC — Administrative Assistant Officer

Association of Cottage Industrialist of Nigeria, Garki, Abuja

October-2016

EDUCATION

Olabisi Onabanjo University, Ogun State — Bs.c Biochemistry

August 2009 - September 2014

PROJECTS

Zuri INc - Team Dugongw Project

Alumni Website generators for tertiary Institution. Link: https://github.com/zuri-training/TeamDugong

SKILLS

Html

CSS.

JavaScript

Node JS

AWARDS

Best Trainee in the Weevil Company/ GIZ one month Programme on Frontend Development (Html and CSS)

LANGUAGES

English, Yoruba